hello welcome to newest permafrost War
crew my name is mik and I'm Pavo and we
just wanted to show you the newest
newest state of the game of course this
is not the final version so just keep in
mind guys that there are things that
will change so just to just so you know
okay so what do we have here Mo this is
the new starting zone yeah yeah entirely
different uh let's look at the map I
think we are starting with from entirely
different uh position than in the in the
demo okay yeah much more to the West now
and what is here I see the freezing
River and there is some kind of thick
Blue Fog oh yeah so it's probably the
place we should avoid for now yeah yeah
and there is a second Road and there are
a few crates to loot so let's see let's
see let's start our adventure this
pretty cold even though we're not in the
cold Zone it's minus minus 21° so yeah
yeah the the world suffered a global
catastrophe even though you can live
there it's still hard very harsh yeah
pretty hard okay we can see in the
background there's a crashed Moon maybe
there will be a place where we can see
it better but yeah that's that's what
caused all of this is that correct yeah
yeah and he he's kind of ominous he he
whenever you go this moon like stares at
you and maybe he will crack even more in
the future so let's let's stay vigilant
and look look to the sky okay we got a
mule here so maybe I will talk to
him okay hello mu you don't look too
good okay thank you that's that's not
very nice of you where are you heading
it's none of their business whatever you
say but dress like that he wasn't very
kind now he asked questions a small camp
run by okay where you standing is now
okay it's Hill Vil this is a small camp
so yeah the people survived even though
it's so cold
people yeah okay uh ask if they can help
you with better gear okay so this is a
side quest let's start by crafting some
pickax okay he's asking us to craft some
pickaxe okay so we need to gather some
resources to do this Stone okay I I
think I scavenged a little bit so I can
craft one pickaxe and then second one I
could uh okay you can do too okay good
good good yeah oh okay I leveled up
crafting uh when I crafted uh so it may
be useful
to uh to do activities as they can
change a little bit okay yeah and we can
unlock new recipes yes for for crafting
other stuff oh yeah yeah uh it wasn't in
the demo so we can um try it later so I
left you a stone pickaxe in the snow
okay uh oh check the blueprints okay we
can also level up the building there's a
crafting menu and building menu so we
got two separates uh separate XP so we
can gather and and unlock new
things okay okay so maybe we can
specialize in different things and you
will probably good idea onep and me
other uh okay so I you dro the pickaxe
okay we can
uh let's let's check if we can indeed
dig it yeah yeah the quest can you dig
it oh it's hard to it's slippery in here
so it's hard to jump okay I got some
vein it's rock Boulder okay so it's not
a vein but still okay I'm gathering
rocks yeah level up pickaxes okay nice
so it probably helps us Gathering stuff
faster okay uh okay and I need to talk
to mule again so let's do this and yeah
and we need to craft better equipment to
cross the river okay so that's the main
quest oh it's nice that the snow just
melting around the brazer it's a cool
detail and I also like the like the
trucks that we're living on the snow
this is
cool we should have an emote like you
know to just lay on the snow and do the
eagle that would be amazing yeah yeah
that that would be awesome okay uh
Gathering resources is the key okay for
crafting better gear okay and we need to
craft the axe okay so maybe I will try
to do this now so Stone axe okay now I
can craft one for you so let's do this
oh teamwork yeah yeah you specialize in
pickaxes I specialize in axes nice okay
so I should drop it yeah thank you drop
it like a star Drop It Like a Star okay
let's gather some more wood okay we need
the wood we need to fire the brazer
chop chop chop chop a lot of level up
axes I think you're getting a little bit
better watch out that was close that was
close sorry sorry I should scream Timber
something like this
sorry okay so we need to light the braer
okay let's do this come
on he's a lazy
one
okay okay so we got the brazer and I
will talk to Mu thanks for the war
greatest friend these days don't for oh
fire is Humanity's greatest friend right
now yeah that's true thank you promus
thank you for it you also need to look
around we remember we remember okay
Stone Shi okay so now we need some some
knife something like this can I craft it
oh I can I can Okay so let's do this
separately now yeah each one having a
knife okay okay so uh find clove okay
where where can we find it maybe we
should enter this Village maybe there's
let's try
it oh okay there is a hunted deer I need
to hunt the deer in the nearby forest
and bring the food back to the mule okay
so we need to find clove and bring some
food but let's check this Village first
or maybe I should say Camp it's probably
more of a camp see a friendly face hello
hello see he's very he's very kind he's
talking about friendly faces so oh I got
it oh great oh another one okay isn't
this steing to be honest well they have
a a trash bin so taking from the trash I
don't think it's uh okay um it's a a
crime so okay so we're just a raccoon
just raccoon yeah yeah just looking you
know we uh fired his place uh for him
maybe uh oh man man man come here I got
a military crate and there are two two
Med packs okay I will take one there's
the alcohol okay of course for the
warming uh
purposes and there's a bandage oh and
there are bux I got some scraps and
electric
parts okay Finder
Keepers
nice okay so okay we got oh we need to
feed the dog see the Dog Days okay but
where is the dog oh I see him okay yeah
there he is let's go let's go hey can we
pet the dog it's Rex oh we can pet the
dog okay this is amazing this great Game
of the Year guys okay can you like try
to give him
food angry wolf okay I don't know if he
likes it uh I don't know if I have any
meat in my no I don't have meat do you
have oh that's why we should hunt all
right all right of course hunt for the
dog okay we got the coal okay so
probably it's a better fuel than than
wood oh it's nice and and warm you the
brazer and then you move away and it's
not so good a lot of snow oh look at the
sunset man oh it's amazing nice oh
there's a dog again I think he likes us
hello or maybe he's want our meat you
know hi Rex I just pet him so that's why
he likes
us um okay so but uh do we have
something to hunt those deers we should
craft uh yeah that's probably a good
idea I wanted to go and just try to
smash them with the ax or something yeah
with uh okay but I didn't have any
recipe to
craft to craft the bow see blueprints
crafting uh ask about trading oh we can
trade with him okay oh and he's got some
nice uh nice shoes jackets gloves and so
on so oh nice backpack military backpack
I want one I will try to buy it for 80
bucks okay so the dollars is still in in
the mix guys oh and I can do this okay
equalize it's good nice okay so I bought
the new
backpack want to see it yes true look at
me it's military backpack oh it's
getting
dark yeah yeah we should um not uh go
away from this Village as we are not yet
uh uh
sure uh what dangerous they have I'm
going near the near the brazer man okay
so I'm
crafting uh I don't have a uh enough
level for the arrows okay so maybe we
need to gather or craft some some lower
level stuff first yeah but I unlocked uh
the recipe for for both oh okay I got
two points okay so I will unlock rope
okay so now I can craft ropes but yeah
we we still need some some levels to
unlock wooden
Arrow I I have the I am the crafting man
I I got I I got ourselves uh two balls
oh okay great let's level up quickly
okay okay
yeah yeah I'm you know
I'm I'm a camel I'm just taking you will
be the hunter oh okay okay oh I will
turn on the uh oh yeah we got the
flashlights okay the flashlight where
are you uh yeah in the in the camp so oh
now we can see the moon man oh this is
terrifying but also beautiful to be
honest oh man at the same
time well as you said before if we would
have like Falling Rocks from the Moon
and we could gather it w that would be
amazing like for
real uh okay so I have the bow for you
there give me give me give me okay thank
you and do you have arrows yeah yeah I'm
splitting uh 11 arrows for you okay one
would be enough man but thank you for
not believing in me okay okay you can
not be too sure yeah those those
comebacks can be a little bit fast so
well now we can have 11 deers so you
know yeah so let's look around if we
find
any hello Rex
again okay maybe they're asleeping right
now oh I have some issues okay
okay I will come back to you in a second
okay I'm trying to find some deer so
take your
time okay guys let's let's check for
deers oh here's a great place to look at
the
Moon
okay oh that that's definitely creepy
guys like you need to see this man
there's an abandoned city
and this Moon and some
facilities oh and we have a dog so at
least it's not that bad guys yeah yeah
we are not alone the dog is with us oh
man I just walk straight to the to the
deer okay and I scared it oh no I didn't
see
it okay it just was right in front of my
face oh no and I think it just jump to
the to the hole oh no I can't see it
it's so dark oh but there are some glowy
like rocks to to mine I don't know what
it
is okay I'm I'm I'm going uh in your
direction okay I came back from my
little Adventure okay uh but where are
you oh okay I see you you are on the
like I'm flashing like like house right
now I'm trying I'm trying okay yeah look
at this man oh okay yeah yeah it's a bit
disturbing to to be honest like seeing
all this stuff yeah I wonder if we will
go there someday it was
oh once I was an adventurer but then I
took an arrow to the knee you believe it
you won't believe
it random guy in
solars and the arrow in the eye and this
is how you started another War man oh I
I have to the first Arrow oh we got the
rock shards and so on so going to gather
it if we won't find any deer we going to
eat
rocks yeah
yeah uh but is there any any yeah I see
see oh yeah there are there are I see
them okay okay okay okay let's take a
bow oh but they are running yeah they
saw you so they scared man yeah yeah I
think I got one yeah yeah but I like
shot completely blindly I didn't yeah so
you're the badass
okay oh okay I HD it lying on the floor
man I think I hit it did you shoot
no oh man I was lying and I hit it I I I
think this is this is a double
kill oh there's so so much meat in here
and bones and everything okay oh now now
you can feed
let can can you like try to like you you
he thinks he you will feed him but then
you say no or no I don't want to do this
why would you do this just to like
check wa wait I guess no harm in feeding
you okay so I can feed it or stop
sniffing my meat I won't give you this
juicy bone no you want you want me to
pick the second option no why maybe you
will change this later but I want to
okay but but you're a monster man oh sad
wolf no man oh no what she taking d
right now
no but he didn't e anything what is he
doing Rex okay let's feed it no happy
wolf
see okay man so now we we have a
dog oh and he's he's got an
inventory so I can put some stuff in him
like bandages and so on okay so let it
be other Behavior
options oh okay just clicked too fast oh
he can search for useful items or warn
about
danger okay maybe let's try him to
search for the items okay yeah yeah sure
we can of course pet him I'm wondering
if I need to like like feed him
regularly or
something yeah yeah probably well he's a
dog he's a dog okay and we need to bring
some ra meat to The Mule okay so let's
bring
it let's go yeah I I'm I think I'm
hungry a little bit so maybe I don't eat
meat man definitely don't eat dog head
over to if you Haven
can take whatever you need it'll oh we
can check his crate in Village okay okay
thank them for their help if you need
anything you know where to find me good
luck on your journey okay oh so that's
all okay so we need to collect the
reward but we need to find his chest to
be honest I was looting some chests here
so I don't know if I didn't pick the
reward
earlier well uh let's let's find out
then uh but I think I also saw some uh
some lady here uh under this uh like uh
under tent construction yeah yeah so
maybe there are some suitcase
here okay man I can't find it so I will
leave it for now so let's talk to talk
let's try to talk to this woman oh yeah
why are you shooting man oh sorry I just
practicing you know did you hit anything
no but if you like just shoot things uh
you actually improve your bow handling
oh you're living up even though you
didn't hit anything okay oh I got a
potato from from her okay uh I don't
have any wood so uh I will chop a little
bit so we have some fuel okay we need to
cook this potato we got a campire here
okay I got some wood so I can I can use
it okay but I would rather to eat some
meat not the potato you know ah okay the
primary okay so the primary slot is for
me yeah yeah yeah yeah exactly so you
can mix up uh your dishes a little bit
okay and there's another slot so I can
add another vegetable probably or
something like this maybe edible roots
no okay no I think edible roots is also
like primary thing you can mix it with
potato oh wait maybe I need to turn on
the fire
first okay yeah there is a warming dish
you can pick it up okay warming dish
okay nice let me see this a dish that
keeps you warm in cold conditions oh so
it gives me the the freezing endurance
and of course
hunger okay so let's eat it nice you
want some
too uh yeah sure I'm a little bit hungry
okay so let's add it cook okay oh thank
you man you're life saer I will do some
more so we can have it
okay I can click with shift so it's
convenient okay oh there will be a
sunrise soon so oh yeah oh look at the
Moon right now oh man yeah yeah I love
this
View and the Colors oh
man if not for the apocalypse that would
be pretty amazing to be here
yeah some ski cord something like this
but it is how it is so yeah I'm just
trying to survive oh we need to talk to
Robin again
okay oh I'm pretty tired right now it
would be nice to go to sleep even though
it's morning right now yeah
yeah maybe use some space they have or
maybe it actually tastes good
okay oh the elements you combined make a
big difference okay build a Shel oh it's
a perfect time to build shelter okay but
I want to sleep I want to sleep but when
we build the shelter you will then have
uh have a place to sleep yeah they don't
want us to sleep in there in their Camp
yeah maybe restricted space or something
like that something like
this okay let's try to get some wood and
let's start building we need to oh you
build a foundation okay you got it okay
Wood Walls go away okay so I can bring
you some wood if you want to
build yeah yeah I gathered some wood
earlier when you were talking so oh and
we will have a a
window I don't know if that's a good
idea but okay sure why
not you must appreciate the view
sometimes to enjoy the view okay let me
see or maybe I'll build another
Foundation oh no we can't build it
because of the tree trunk can I destroy
it yeah let's let's destroy
it I don't know if I can destroy this
one no no the the TR the trunk I think
it might not be destroy destroyable so
maybe let's build like a you know like a
Tetris block or something like this that
would be fun yeah yeah like I never
built this like this house before so in
that shape so that's a new one that's a
new one
okay then we can just add another blocks
and they will fit together so
yeah I I I like this uh uh shape
actually I I've never like build a yeah
me too but I don't know if that's very
like space efficient
but but still if it works it works it
works yeah yeah exactly
okay so now we need
some some place to sleep workbench I
want to
sleep enough work I don't have
unlocked uh then we we we would uh craft
and place a sleep B in workbench ah okay
so okay so we need to work first okay
yeah but I will unlock the campfire okay
I got the workbench so I can build the
workbench yeah I also wondering if there
are tools that are like
um I need wood okay better than uh than
this like starting stone pickaxe maybe
we can craft in workbench some refined
tools or a yeah that's a good idea but I
want to sleep man I'm very tired yeah
yeah we should we should it's already
morning we actually worked all night
that's a weird feeling usually i' I'm
playing all night but working all night
that's a new one that's a new one yeah
but on the bright side we survived a
first day in permafrost yeah that's true
and we have a dog and some friends I
don't know if there are friends we
cannot sleep in their house
so yeah maybe uh we shouldn't trust them
yet
yeah maybe that was poison
tomato oh it was potato okay poisonous
potato all right so I'll try to build
the
workbench I
will maybe build a stairs
so oh man I'm I'm blind I was like
scrolling five times through the list of
building and I couldn't find a workbench
okay but I got it now all right and
maybe some oh no it's too cold to
interact okay let's build a campfire
here yeah yeah you see there's actually
a snow underneath the work yeah okay
maybe somewhere here near the entrance
yeah yeah maybe yes maybe there sorry
can you can you okay yeah yeah uh do you
need some wood or no I'm fine I'm fine
it's okay
okay uh maybe 15 Wood is a bit too much
oh I dropped it yeah but I dropped it
here okay let it be okay
nice yeah now I can use it could can you
uh craft this uh no but I don't see the
sleeping back maybe I need to unlock it
first yeah yeah I think that's the case
let's let's see where it is yeah it's
it's on the third level uh on on the the
right CRA thing oh yeah sleeping back
okay I don't have enough points no I
have five points so maybe level yeah but
I don't have level okay yeah yeah so we
need to craft a little bit more so no
sleep No Sleep till Brooklyn not not yet
but we are very close Okay but I can
like craft the basic tools and so on and
then I will level
up yeah yeah let's try it you just like
honing in your craft yeah oh and I found
some uh some Stone so it will be C
crafting Stone axes yeah crafting level
up okay level up okay that's cool
and now can I do
this crafting level three okay I got
sleeping bags whoop whoop nice nice
bandages okay that may be useful okay so
now oh it's too cold okay because I took
the wood from the camp I'm I'm sorry I
left you I'm just uh collecting stone I
have a lot of stone now okay this is a
cooperation like you know I'm crafting
sleeping bags Gathering Stones I'm
making myself useful to this small
community of you and
me so yeah okay so maybe I will uh build
us oh no but somehow I build it on the
on the workstation you know yeah yeah
you can you can just pick it up okay
let's do this don't sleep on the table
man what okay I got sleeping back you
can pick this one too ah okay so you
craft something and it's on the table to
pick it up okay that makes
sense oh all right but sleeping on a
table you know be isolated so I I I have
a sleeping B I will close the doors so
we get some privacy here okay and we can
sleep can you place uh yeah yeah I'm
working on it okay I can rotate it near
the window I don't know it's that's a
good idea so we can share one uh
sleeping bag I don't mind man first you
should buy me a drink or something like
you
know okay be here okay I was trying to
put it here but the roof was not
cooperating so okay let's go to sleep
yeah so it will be night right right now
probably oh it's a sunset okay nice nice
oh but I'm I'm hungry now yeah so I I
will cook some meat for us okay okay I
got I still got this warm dish so I will
eat it not that I'm not trusting you or
something I also cooked some edible
roots oh
nice oh when when
you
uh what you have when you cook edible
root what you get you get energy dish
okay so these roots are kind of like you
know
kicking oh okay edible root but did you
add the potato to it just Roots just
Roots yeah
okay okay so energy dish yeah okay so
let's uh let's talk uh with Robin Robin
okay we expanded this Village a little
bit now so now now we need to conquer H
Wily Wily Hil how was
it okay uh okay so we can collect reward
but now we need to find her chest
where is it where could it be
tailoring so that's for some crafting
stuff okay maybe
uh maybe check this out oh okay this
this chest is working okay Quest
reward okay but I I had some recipe that
I already own okay and put on Renegades
code ooh so we
Renegades okay okay did it unlock the
recipe for us yeah yeah you actually can
skip the the level requirements if you
do the quest Oh okay that's cool okay so
I guess we need to find it in a
workbench or yeah Renegade Cod and I can
craft them okay I will craft two okay
cold resistance 28 yeah yeah I'm
crafting do you have enough like cloth
yeah yeah man nice I was Scavenging the
the whole village okay I put it up looks
cool you are so fast to pick it up from
the table man yeah yeah like just a bit
too fast you know just a bit too fast I
was
cold okay so now we renates
man okay collect but okay we again have
to collect the reward but from Robin or
maybe from the chest I will see the
chest can collect from the chest no the
chest is not available maybe from
Robin yeah but uh I think we are
um I can ask if she needs any help oh
she needs some help oh
okay Liam Liam niss okay
nice okay so we need to find Liam but
any any information about it
maybe some marker on the map or maybe
let's check the quest
log ah check on Liam up on the hill okay
so there's probably only one Hill here
on the North this one
maybe yeah yeah let's let's find this
guy there's a light inside here no I
found it light yeah I think we uh we
must do a little bit of a
jumping
puzzle it's getting dark I don't know if
if jumping on a sleepy Rock in the dark
is a good idea to be honest oh there is
some kind of new uh Boulder with a flint
okay we can try to pick it up Flint
Shard
okay what a
teamwork let's
go this is the the river below us yeah
yeah maybe there is some of like a
shortcut or something
yeah okay but let's find a some way up
maybe maybe there is maybe a
ladder no maybe a no
ladder there should be a way somewhere
maybe I'm not seeing it let's try to
move
around let's look for something
okay there are some stones to jump
on okay that's a start okay I'm getting
up man okay
okay okay I'm following you okay there
is rock rock Boulder but I will leave it
oh I got some
freeze okay it's
fine okay I'm I'm oh that was not a good
idea okay but maybe
here like if you try but I I did the
roll
so okay okay okay okay are you okay yeah
yeah I'm good I'm good I'm all good okay
okay okay I'm jumping
up we're getting somewhere we're getting
somewhere yeah we are doing great
there's a rock Shard okay maybe here no
maybe this way
oh okay you you found something yeah I
think it's a path okay okay let's go
well at least we're moving on okay okay
yeah yeah but there's nothing here so
maybe a bit maybe a a bit down now down
or up oh there is a tent actually where
where H uh oh oh oh there's a tent okay
oh is that Liam it's present body I'm
okay gu look at this Moon from this like
side
yeah I must say he's got the
view that's okay let's uh there is some
guy that looks like he Frozen there's
some kind of recording can you listen to
there's a backpack casual
backpack okay but I SWA the backpack
okay I will leave it
probably here for body yeah you got some
tape I left the packpack here so maybe
it would be better than yours I don't
know recording I can't on like this uh
do you hear it yeah yeah okay okay
recording our favorite place we'd pitch
a tent here spend the night staring at
that damn Moon I wish you could come
back
here just one more time so he's missing
someone miss you so
much okay oh yeah the quest the quest is
completed so yeah that was that was Li I
think he he couldn't handle the pressure
of yeah probably we got the
call man I'm I'm a terrible person oh no
Liam died oh we got a call here
anyway oh yeah
yeah okay but you know someone else died
so so we can survive yeah Live Another
Day that's true we need to fight but
yeah there's some some coal here and
other stuff there flints coal Coal
should be a great thing for for fueling
uh brazers Etc another coal Boulder
let's
go coal will will keep the cold away you
know Flint Boulder Rock boulder oh
there's a look there's a pickaxe Flint
pickaxe okay wa nice finder
keeper show me what you got damage 12 oh
so it's a better pickaxe good okay this
is almost destroyed so I will leave it
here maybe someone will find it some
other way yeah yeah and we could repair
it later but yeah for now let's let's
head back to the camp I guess it's
easier said than done but let's try
let's let's look for the safest route
there should be like you know like like
hay or something then we should do the
leap of
Fate that would help a lot okay we need
to go just the same way as we climb
probably I I will experiment a little
bit you will jump no don't do this you
you got the whole life in front oh there
is there is a lot of stone actually
okay there's like a hidden passage I
think oh okay
I don't know if I'm alive okay but that
yeah but that
hurts okay I will talk to
Robin what's up report back about Liam
that's horrible that's horrible days
I'll ask someone to
help they will they will bury him I'm s
for dragging you into this yeah poor
guy okay collect reward
okay but again I don't know if I can get
it from the chest or from
Robin let's uh let's try the chest maybe
no it's not this maybe there's another
chest but we don't know where this was
probably the the mule chest but I'm not
exactly sure but
okay okay can we craft some some better
gear to actually try and and cross the
river yeah yeah I think so uh crafting
oh you asked about the better uh like
better tools to use and yeah on fourth
level there is refined stone pickaxe and
Axe and shave and so on then later
there's Flint
axe oh and the Renegade codes yeah you
were right it's on the level six so so
we can use it right away good oh there
are zip
ties scrub ax improvise te
quality pickaxe SMG trap B oh there's so
many things to craft
man
okay and also the building man there's
also some things to
craft okay okay so I almost wondering if
uh if our clothes didn't um deteriorate
a little bit but no it's uh it's good so
but there is a durability status so
maybe they can wear off somehow but
maybe not now maybe the weather isn't
cold enough to like you know destroy the
thing okay mate so I think that will be
enough for today's session and we can
leave The Crossing for the next time but
we did some progress I must say we got a
house we got better clothes we got a dog
we met some people met a few friends
yeah so that was a pretty good session
to be honest Hest yeah yeah let's uh see
what brings us the future and uh I hope
it stays uh it will be a little bit
warmer H yeah so we need to stay calm
okay guys so thank you for for watching
and we hope to see you soon in another
adventures in permafrost so have a great
day and stay stay hot stay safe yeah May
the fire uh guide you yeah praise the
Sun and so on yeah
okay thank you guys bye-bye